Privacy Policy
==============

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘ Personal Data or Personally Identifiable  
Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact,  
or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding  
of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

#### What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website?

#### Personal Data

Our Site may contain registration forms (e.g. during customer support and review) that will ask users at their discretion to provide us  
with contact information such as their name, address, e-mail address and username. We use this information to send you news and updates  
and promotional material about our products or from some of our partners. We do not pass this information to third parties other than the  
people/or associate working with the product or website.

Users may opt out of any unwanted emails by the remove option in the emails or by contacting us directly

#### Anonymous Information (“Non-personal Data”):

Additionally, we collect and/or receive and store certain non-personal information (“Non-personal Data”) whenever you interact with us.  
Non-personal Data does not permit the identification of individual persons. This exchange of information occurs between your browser and  
our affiliates or our server occurs automatically upon accessing our pages. Through such exchange, we receive Non-personal Data including without  
limitation, data relating to the browser you are using, mobile/desktop device, general properties and metadata, OS version, preferred language, the  
date and time of your visit, the referring website and your preferences in our Websites during your visit. We collect such statistical information  
about usage as aggregate data from the Site in order to maintain a better customer experience.

#### When do we collect information?

We collect personal data from you when you fill out a form or enter information on our site.

We collect anonymous information automatically upon your accessing of our site. Additionally, our website may use 3rd parties such  
as Google Analytics and third-party analytics to better understand how you use the Site and ways that we can improve your experience.  
Through this tool, we can see trends of usage of our Site such as total number of unique users, popular webpages or articles by number  
of total impressions, etc. These third parties use pixels or cookies to measure things such as the average time spent by users on the  
Site or visited pages so we learn how to improve the Site for you.

To learn more how Google uses data from our use of Google Analytics Cookie we recommend you review Google’s policies located at:  
[www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners](https://www.theonlineuserprotector.com/). We also encourage you to review  
the Google Analytics’ currently available opt-outs for the web tool available at:  
[https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/](https://www.theonlineuserprotector.com/).

#### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing  
communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

* To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
* To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
* To follow up with you after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)
* To enforce the Terms of Service
* Customer Analytics

Additionally, we may provide Personal Information and Anonymous Information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other third  
parties for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf mainly for statistic purposes. We require that such parties maintain  
the confidentiality of such information. We may also use your email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding our services.  
You may choose not to receive email of this type by following the unsubscribe link contained in the email provided.

We, independently and/or via our authorized service providers, may collect Anonymous Information during the use of the Site and its services. We  
may use Anonymous Information or disclose it to third party service providers, to improve our services, to enhance your experience with the Site and  
its services and to offer new services from time to time.

We may disclose your Personal Information or any information you submitted via the Site and its services if we have a good faith belief that  
disclosure of such information is helpful or reasonably necessary to (i) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental  
request, (ii) enforce any agreements we may have with you including investigations of potential violations thereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or  
otherwise address fraud or security issues, (iv) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of our Company, its users, yourself or the  
public, (v) to respond to claims that any content published on the Site or the services violates any right of a third-party, (vi) to respond to claims  
that unauthorized information (e.g. name, etc.) of a third-party has been posted on the Site or the services, (vii) when our Company is undergoing any  
change in control, including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of all or substantially all of the assets of our Company (viii) pursuant to  
your approval, in order to supply certain services you have requested from our Company (ix) to collect, hold and manage your Personal Information  
through a third party’s cloud based services, as reasonable for business purposes, which may be located in countries outside of your jurisdiction,  
including but not limited to the United States of America.

#### How do we protect your information?

We take a great care in maintaining the security of the Site, its services and your information and in preventing unauthorized access to it through  
industry standard technologies and internal procedures, including through the use of tokens and encryption mechanisms. However, we do not guarantee  
that unauthorized access will never occur.

#### Do we use ‘cookies’?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow)  
that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. They are also used to  
help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use  
cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the  
future.

Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until  
its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user  
session, when the web browser is closed.

#### We use cookies to:

* When you submit data to through a form such as those found on contact pages or comment forms cookies may be set to remember your user  
    details for future correspondence.
* In order to provide you with a great experience on this site we provide the functionality to set your preferences for how this site runs  
    when you use it. To remember your preferences, we need to set cookies so that this information can be called whenever you interact with a page is  
    affected by your preferences.
* Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf. The following section details which third party cookies  
you might encounter through this site. This site uses Google Analytics, which is one of the most widespread and trusted analytics solution on the  
web for helping us to understand how you use the site and ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track things such as how long  
you spend on the site and the pages that you visit so we can continue to produce engaging content.

For more information on Google Analytics cookies, see the official Google Analytics page  
([https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage](https://www.theonlineuserprotector.com/))

#### How to disable cookies

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your  
browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly. It won’t affect the user’s  
experience that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.

#### Third-party disclosure

We do not share, sell, rent or trade your personal information with third parties other than as disclosed within this privacy policy. We may  
disclose your personal data to any member of our group of companies (this means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and all its  
subsidiaries) insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this policy.

#### Third-party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products (including affiliate companies’) or services on our website.  
These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and  
activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### Your rights

Your principal rights under data protection law in relation to your Persona Data are:

* the right to access and information;
* the right to rectification;
* the right to erasure;
* the right to restrict processing;
* the right to object to processing;
* the right to data portability;
* the right to complain to a supervisory authority; and
* the right to withdraw consent.

We provide you with the ability to exercise certain choices and controls in connection with our treatment of your Personal Data.  
Depending on your relationship with us, these choices and controls may include, access to the Personal Data collected about you that we hold;  
correcting, updating or deleting the information associated with you that we hold; and in the event, you wish to opt out from the data collection  
or you are not able to exerciser your rights through your account please contact us. In the event you make such request, note that we  
may require certain information from you in order to verify your identity and locate your data and that the process of locating and deleting the  
data may take reasonable time and effort. Data privacy and related laws in your jurisdiction may provide you with different or additional rights  
related to the data we collect from you, which may also apply.

Should you need any additional information about your rights please feel free to contact us

#### Children’s Privacy

You represent and warrant that you are at least 13 years of age and of legal competence to use our Site. If you are under 18, please be sure to  
read the Agreement with your parents or legal guardians. We do not use the Site to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age  
of thirteen (13). We request that such individuals do not provide Personal Data through our services. If you become aware or have any reason to  
believe that a child under the age of 13 has shared any information with us, please contact us and we take reasonable steps to ensure  
that such information is deleted from our files.

#### Data Retention

We may rectify, replenish or remove incomplete or inaccurate information, at any time and at our own discretion as detailed above. Please note  
that unless you instruct us otherwise we retain the information we collect for as long as needed to comply with our legal obligations, resolve  
disputes and enforce our agreements.

#### Policy Updates

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem  
appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Thus,  
we encourage you to check this Privacy Policy regularly for updates, so that you are fully informed on how your data is collected and used by the  
Company and your related rights. The last revision date will be reflected in the “Last Modified” heading.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy,  
we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the change becoming effective.

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

Email:

[\[email protected\]](https://www.theonlineuserprotector.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  

Data protection officer
